(Sheldon:)...to hold back the few superior men.
(Leonard:)That actually does help.
(Sheldon:)It's worth noting
that he died of syphilis.
(Leonard:)Screw it, I'm going.
(Sheldon:)On your way home,
will you pick up orange juice?
(Leonard:)Do you mind? I'm questioning
a lot of things in my Iife.
(Sheldon:)Is one of those things
your fondness for orange juice?
(Sheldon:)- No.
- Great. Tropicana, no pulp.
- Hey, Sheldon.
Who is it?
(Sheldon:)It's me, Sheldon, Mrs. Wolowitz.
(Howard:)That's not my mom. It's Bernadette.
(Sheldon:)Really? That's very unsettling.
- Hi, Sheldon.
- Hi.
(Penny:)- What's up?
- It just occurred to me...
(Sheldon:)...that I never formally congratulated you
on your pending nuptials.
(Sheldon:)I hopped on the first bus and hightailed
it down here to shake your hand.